(this.webpackJsonpmilionaire=this.webpackJsonpmilionaire||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,c){},12:function(e,t,c){"use strict";c.r(t);var r=c(0),n=c.n(r),o=c(5),a=c.n(o),s=c(2),i=(c(10),c(1));function u(e){var t=e.setUsername,c=Object(r.useRef)();return Object(i.jsxs)("div",{className:"start",children:[Object(i.jsx)("input",{className:"startInput",placeholder:"enter your name",ref:c}),Object(i.jsx)("button",{className:"startButton",onClick:function(){c.current.value&&t(c.current.value)},children:"Start"})]})}function l(e){var t=e.setTimeOut,c=e.questionNumber,n=Object(r.useState)(30),o=Object(s.a)(n,2),a=o[0],i=o[1];return Object(r.useEffect)((function(){if(0===a)return t(!0);var e=setInterval((function(){i((function(e){return e-1}))}),1e3);return function(){return clearInterval(e)}}),[a,t]),Object(r.useEffect)((function(){i(30)}),[c]),a}var d=c(3),m=c.p+"static/media/play.8e5f6d1d.mp3",h=c.p+"static/media/correct.160572d7.mp3",x=c.p+"static/media/wrong.e9468218.mp3";function j(e){var t=e.data,c=e.questionNumber,n=e.setQuestionNumber,o=e.setTimeOut,a=Object(r.useState)(null),u=Object(s.a)(a,2),l=u[0],j=u[1],b=Object(r.useState)(null),f=Object(s.a)(b,2),O=f[0],p=f[1],v=Object(r.useState)("answer"),w=Object(s.a)(v,2),y=w[0],N=w[1],g=Object(d.a)(m),S=Object(s.a)(g,1)[0],q=Object(d.a)(h),$=Object(s.a)(q,1)[0],k=Object(d.a)(x),I=Object(s.a)(k,1)[0];Object(r.useEffect)((function(){S()}),[S]),Object(r.useEffect)((function(){j(t[c-1])}),[t,c]);var W=function(e,t){setTimeout((function(){t()}),e)};return Object(i.jsxs)("div",{className:"trivia",children:[Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:null===l||void 0===l?void 0:l.question}),Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"answers",children:null===l||void 0===l?void 0:l.answers.map((function(e){return Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:O===e?y:"answer",onClick:function(){return!O&&function(e){p(e),N("answer active"),W(3e3,(function(){N(e.correct?"answer correct":"answer wrong")})),W(5e3,(function(){e.correct?($(),W(1e3,(function(){n((function(e){return e+1})),p(null)}))):(I(),W(1e3,(function(){o(!0)})))}))}(e)},children:e.text})}))})]})}var b=function(){var e=Object(r.useState)(null),t=Object(s.a)(e,2),c=t[0],n=t[1],o=Object(r.useState)(!1),a=Object(s.a)(o,2),d=a[0],m=a[1],h=Object(r.useState)(1),x=Object(s.a)(h,2),b=x[0],f=x[1],O=Object(r.useState)("$ 0"),p=Object(s.a)(O,2),v=p[0],w=p[1],y=Object(r.useMemo)((function(){return[{id:1,amount:"$ 100"},{id:2,amount:"$ 200"},{id:3,amount:"$ 300"},{id:4,amount:"$ 500"},{id:5,amount:"$ 1.000"},{id:6,amount:"$ 2.000"},{id:7,amount:"$ 4.000"},{id:8,amount:"$ 8.000"},{id:9,amount:"$ 16.000"},{id:10,amount:"$ 32.000"},{id:11,amount:"$ 64.000"},{id:12,amount:"$ 125.000"},{id:13,amount:"$ 250.000"},{id:14,amount:"$ 500.000"},{id:15,amount:"$ 1.000.000"}].reverse()}),[]);return Object(r.useEffect)((function(){b>1&&w(y.find((function(e){return e.id===b-1})).amount)}),[b,y]),Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:c?Object(i.jsxs)(i.Fragment,{children:[Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"main",children:d?Object(i.jsxs)("h1",{className:"endText",children:["You earned: ",v]}):Object(i.jsxs)(i.Fragment,{children:[Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"top",children:Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"timer",children:Object(i.jsx)(l,{setTimeOut:m,questionNumber:b})})}),Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"bottom",children:Object(i.jsx)(j,{data:[{id:1,question:"Rolex is a company that specializes in what type of product?",answers:[{text:"Phone",correct:!1},{text:"Watches",correct:!0},{text:"Food",correct:!1},{text:"Cosmetic",correct:!1}]},{id:2,question:"When did the website `Facebook` launch?",answers:[{text:"2004",correct:!0},{text:"2005",correct:!1},{text:"2006",correct:!1},{text:"2007",correct:!1}]},{id:3,question:"Who played the character of harry potter in movie?",answers:[{text:"Johnny Deep",correct:!1},{text:"Leonardo Di Caprio",correct:!1},{text:"Denzel Washington",correct:!1},{text:"Daniel Red Cliff",correct:!0}]},{id:4,question:"What is the pH value of the human body?",answers:[{text:"9.2 to 9.8",correct:!1},{text:"7.2 to 8.2",correct:!1},{text:"5.2 to 6.8",correct:!1},{text:"7.0 to 7.8",correct:!0}]},{id:5,question:" Which of the following are called Key Industrial animals?",answers:[{text:"Producers",correct:!1},{text:"Tertiary consumers",correct:!1},{text:"Primary consumers",correct:!0},{text:"None of these",correct:!1}]},{id:6,question:" Which of the given amendments made it compulsory for the president to consent to the constitutional Amendment bills?",answers:[{text:"27th",correct:!1},{text:"24th",correct:!0},{text:"26th",correct:!1},{text:"29th",correct:!1}]},{id:7,question:"Which of the following Himalayan regions is called Shivalik's?",answers:[{text:"Upper Himalayas",correct:!1},{text:"Lower Himalayas",correct:!1},{text:"Outer Himalayas",correct:!0},{text:"Inner Himalayas",correct:!1}]},{id:8,question:"The Samkhya School of Philosophy was founded by?",answers:[{text:"Gautam Buddha",correct:!1},{text:"Mahipala",correct:!1},{text:"Gopala",correct:!1},{text:"Kapila",correct:!0}]},{id:9,question:"Pustaz grasslands are situated at?",answers:[{text:"South Africa",correct:!1},{text:"China",correct:!1},{text:"Hungary",correct:!0},{text:"USA",correct:!1}]},{id:10,question:"Chelaiya Samiti is related to which of the following?",answers:[{text:"Banking sector",correct:!1},{text:"Health Sector",correct:!1},{text:"Tax reforms",correct:!0},{text:"Insurance sector",correct:!1}]},{id:11,question:"Which of the given devices is used for counting blood cells?",answers:[{text:"Hmelethometer",correct:!1},{text:"Spyscometer",correct:!1},{text:"Hemocytometer",correct:!0},{text:"Hamosytometer",correct:!1}]},{id:12,question:"Which of the given compounds is used to make fireproof clothing?",answers:[{text:"Aluminum chloride",correct:!1},{text:"Aluminum Sulphate",correct:!0},{text:"Magnesium Chloride",correct:!1},{text:"Magnesium Sulphate",correct:!1}]},{id:13,question:"Which of the given is a disease caused by protozoa?",answers:[{text:"Cancer",correct:!1},{text:"Typhoid",correct:!1},{text:"Kala-azar",correct:!0},{text:"Chicken Pox",correct:!1}]},{id:14,question:"Which of the given coins was known as 'Karshapana' in ancient literature?",answers:[{text:"Gold coins",correct:!1},{text:"Bronze coins",correct:!1},{text:"Punch marked coins",correct:!0},{text:"Iron coins",correct:!1}]},{id:15,question:"Rashtriya Swasthya Bima Yojana Launched under Social Security Act 2008 Involves?",answers:[{text:"Only rural workers",correct:!1},{text:"Only social workers",correct:!1},{text:"Only Unorganized sector workers",correct:!0},{text:"All of the above",correct:!1}]}],questionNumber:b,setQuestionNumber:f,setTimeOut:m})})]})}),Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"pyramid",children:Object(i.jsx)("ul",{className:"moneyList",children:y.map((function(e){return Object(i.jsxs)("li",{className:b===e.id?"moneyListItem active":"moneyListItem",children:[Object(i.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemNumber",children:e.id}),Object(i.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemAmount",children:e.amount})]})}))})})]}):Object(i.jsx)(u,{setUsername:n})})};a.a.render(Object(i.jsx)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(i.jsx)(b,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.9e210ba1.chunk.js.map